



Paulina Loor Tubay

Date of birth: 21/09/2002 | **Nationality:** Ecuadorian | **Gender:** Female | **Phone number:**

(+593) 0989163972 (Mobile) | **Email address:** loorpaulinamar@gmail.com | **Website:**

https://loorpaulina.github.io/LoorPaulina/ | LinkedIn:

linkedin.com/in/paulina-loor-tubay-79711a214 | WhatsApp Messenger: 0989163972 |

Address: Coop Juan Montalvo, Mz. 1738 S.1, 090101, Guayaguil, Ecuador

(Home)

ABOUT ME

I am a 22-year-old Computer Science Engineering student with a strong commitment to excellence and punctuality. My meticulous and detail-oriented approach allows me to tackle projects in an organized and efficient manner, always meeting deadlines. I possess technical skills in programming, problem solving and data analysis, and have the ability to adapt quickly to new technologies in a constantly evolving field.

I am excited to contribute to challenging projects and collaborate with professionals in the IT field, with the goal of driving innovation and making a difference in the world of technology.

WORK EXPERIENCE

18/07/2024 - 15/11/2024 Ecuador

JUNIOR FULLSTACK DEVELOPER FUTURE SOFT S.A

—Implementation of ERP Processes using technologies such as React and Flask.

05/2023 - 08/2023 Guayaguil, Ecuador

ACADEMIC ASSISTANT ESCUELA SUPERIOR POLITÉCNICA DEL LITORAL

05/2023 - 02/2024 Guayaquil, Ecuador

MANAGEMENT ASSISTANT ESCUELA SUPERIOR POLITÉCNICA DEL LITORAL

05/2023 - CURRENT Guayaquil, Ecuador

MEMBER OF TAWS WEB, MOBILE AND DATA SCIENCE TECHNOLOGIES RESEARCH GROUP

2018 – 2018 Guayaguil, Ecuador

INTERN CNT

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

2021 - CURRENT Guayaquil, Ecuador

COMPUTER SCIENCE ENGINEER Escuela Superior Politécnica del Litoral

Website https://www.espol.edu.ec/es

2014 - 2019 Guayaquil, Ecuador

TECHNICAL BACHELOR IN SYSTEMS Unidad Educativa Speedwriting

Website https://speedwriting.ec/

DIGITAL SKILLS

Figma (Intermediate) | Angular Framwork | Java | Git | JavaScript | MySQL | Programación python | Ionic Framework | Html/CSS | React | Python Flask (intermediate)

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): **SPANISH**

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production Spoken interaction		
ENGLISH	B1	B2	B1	B1	B2

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

• CERTIFICACIONES Y CURSOS

2020

Introduction to Cybersecurity

CISCO

2023

CCNA: Introduction to Networks

CISCO